tutorialoutpost.com 2014-05-19

# Privacy

Sabotage Media, LLC (“Sabotage Media”) operates several [websites](http://tutorialoutpost.com/privacy#) including **tutorialoutpost.com**. It is Sabotage Media’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Sabotage Media collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and [servers](http://tutorialoutpost.com/privacy#) typically make available, such as the browser type, [language](http://tutorialoutpost.com/privacy#) preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Sabotage Media’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Sabotage Media’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Sabotage Media may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Sabotage Media also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Sabotage Media does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Sabotage Media’s websites choose to interact with Sabotage Media in ways that require Sabotage Media to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Sabotage Media gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account on tutorialoutpost.com to provide a username and [email address](http://tutorialoutpost.com/privacy#). In each case, Sabotage Media collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Sabotage Media. Sabotage Media does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

Sabotage Media may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Sabotage Media may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Sabotage Media does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Sabotage Media discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Sabotage Media’s behalf or to provide services available at Sabotage Media’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Sabotage Media’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Sabotage Media will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Sabotage Media discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Sabotage Media believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Sabotage Media, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a Sabotage Media website and have supplied your [email](http://tutorialoutpost.com/privacy#) address, Sabotage Media may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Sabotage Media and our products. We primarily use our blog to [communicate](http://tutorialoutpost.com/privacy#) this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Sabotage Media takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s [computer](http://tutorialoutpost.com/privacy#), and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Sabotage Media uses cookies to help Sabotage Media identify and track visitors, their usage of Sabotage Media website, and their website access preferences. Sabotage Media visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their [computers](http://tutorialoutpost.com/privacy#) should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Sabotage Media’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Sabotage Media’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Sabotage Media may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Sabotage Media’s sole discretion. Sabotage Media encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
